hey what's up today I want to talk about
the best way to make over $100,000
online in 2024 and going into 2025 as
you know the economy things are crazy
everything costs a lot more than it ever
has and no matter who gets elected
that's not going to change you're going
to have to learn to make more money and
increase your income if you want to keep
up you know statistically if you want to
actually qualify to buy a house in most
cities you got to be making at least
$100 to $200,000 a year and so that's
what I want to talk about today is the
best ways to make money online right now
that are proven that work now what
qualifies me to talk about this well
number one I haven't made less than at
the lowest point a quarter of a million
dollars in the last 10 years every
single year and then number two is that
I've actually been in this industry for
over 21 almost 22 years I've built
personally businesses that have done
over $20
million in the space that I'm in and I
want to walk you through what I think
right now is the best business model and
the best way for you to be able to make
$100,000 on your own imagine what it
would be like if you weren't struggling
with finances or you could literally
just not have to work two jobs to be
able to just pay to survive that's what
we're going to be talking about here
today and I'm going to show you what the
best process is for that now there's a
number of different ways that you can
read about online about making money
whether it be cryptocurrency e-commerce
Airbnb things like that th and while
those things are are great and they can
work um there's really one way that I
know that I think is the best for people
when they're starting out because it
doesn't take a lot of startup cost you
don't need to franchise you don't need
to um have a lot of money you don't need
a big following that's a big
misconception you don't need a ton of
technical skills you actually don't need
any technical skills anymore you did
years ago not anymore and so what that
is is it's the space of online coaching
and courses let me explain this to you
and this is where a lot of people get it
wrong is they're like well why why would
anybody buy a course or coaching from me
chances are that you have experiences in
your life that you've accomplished or
done that solve a problem that somebody
has and so if there's a problem that
somebody has and you know how to fix it
no matter what it is could be Automotive
could be related to video games could be
related to golfing could be related to
hardening you can make $100,000 to
$200,000 easily in your own business
selling a course or training program or
coaching program or membership around
that topic helping other people with
those things I'll tell you this it's a
lot better than
99.9% of the jobs that are out there
that you could be doing and and if you
have technical skills it goes even up
from there you could easily make
millions of dollars if you are already
have certain technical skills in online
marketing and sales and things like that
but even if you're a total newbie and
you don't have those skills1 to $200,000
is super realistic and reasonable now
there is work involved it's not like oh
you don't have to do any work it's not
like you do this one thing and and then
it just makes you all this money there
is like consistent work that you have to
do but the great part is you don't have
to work more than 5 to 10 hours a week
to be able to do it in my in my business
right now I have a toddler and we have a
brand new newborn on the way by the time
this video is published who knows the
baby might be born and so I don't have a
lot of time to work to build my business
and yet I have a seven figure
multi-million dollar business and it's
in the space of online courses coaching
and mentoring now when I got started in
this industry we sold CD and DVD
products now it's such a blessing that
we can do all of this on the internet
you record something on your computer
you can record it on your phone you can
upload it and then you can find people
that need that problem solved and sell
it to
them the how do you find those people
social media YouTube those are the two
best ways that we use to find people to
work with in our business that's why I
make videos like this all the time and
and so even though I have trainings and
courses and things like that like we
just literally just finished putting
together and launching today over my
website where it says free classes a
brand new course right here whoops
that's that's the last that's the
previous one that we had this one right
here called start your own sixf figure
online course or coaching business it's
a brand new free class all about how to
make $10 to $225,000 a month if you are
ambitious and ready to take action but
you don't know where to start to build
this out and so you can check this out
it's a 42-minute in-depth training where
I dive deep into the nuances of what it
actually takes to be able to do that so
you can find the link below in this
description or you can go find it on my
website over at jeremi Kowski
docomo up in our head like do I actually
have something of value to offer to
people why would people want to buy
something from me why would people want
to work with me and so can I tell you
this is that one of the biggest things
that we have to do in order to get
started on this journey is we need to
address our own internal dialogue that
we have and our own self-belief around
is it possible for me here's the thing
if you don't think it's possible for you
it probably won't be but it's also
probably because you don't know what I
know which is what I share with you in
the training that's what I share with
you on this YouTube channel where I'm
literally giving you the the knowledge
and the information that you need to be
able to accomplish that the only reason
why you're not at the place where I'm at
is because you just don't know the
things that I know and it's not
complicated it's not difficult and what
I've done is I've actually created my
own business of passing on all of the
lessons that I know to you so that you
can learn them very simply very easily
so what you want to do is when you start
one of these businesses you want to
figure out who is the person that you
can help the most a lot of people call
this finding their Niche and then what
you can do is you figure out what are
the problems that they have and how can
you solve them for them there are people
right now who have problems that you
absolutely can solve and then what you
do is you start to talk
about those not those just those
problems but those
solutions that you have to offer
out there to people and help start
solving those problems this is one of
the biggest kind of misconceptions about
this type of a business is that again
you don't need to wait until you have a
big following or or a bunch of people
that are already buying from you to be
able to do this the best way to get
started is you literally just start
talking about it to people on your
social media you can create some YouTube
videos about it you can start to grow an
email list and then you can create an
offer that is an irresistible offer that
solves this problem for somebody you're
able to package it in a way that they
want that they desire okay and so what
you do is you look at is what is that
solution and then what are the things
that people actually want and desire and
here's the best way to know what that is
you ask them and they will tell you the
more you interact and connect with
people and I get it maybe if you've not
done this before this might sound
daunting this might sound complicated
how am I going to find people to
interact with and con con with well
that's where the work is involved and
that's exactly what I coach people on
inside of my program it's exactly what I
walk you through in all of the trainings
that I put together is how to find those
people and be able to bring them into
your ecosystem but the best way to do
this is this is the process that I call
find promote and close it's a three-step
process that we've invented that works
every single time in these businesses
okay so number one you want to find who
those people are and where do they hang
out what books do they read what groups
do they on on social media and it's not
that you're going out there to spam
people or you're trying to go like DM or
message people to get them to become in
your business I don't personally do that
at all what I believe is that you can
actually attract those people to you by
learning what do they care about and
immersing yourself in the world of the
person whose problem that you can solve
so if you start to get to know what are
the life experiences of those people
that you can solve problems for you can
learn how to do the Second Step which is
promote and offer to them and I believe
that you need to do what we call an
experimentation process where you do an
alpha release where you don't have to
create the whole thing you don't have to
do all this work to put it all together
but you can actually find the people
solve the problem very simply before you
put everything together and test run the
whole thing in that training that I put
together that's exactly what I walk you
through as well you can go find it again
in this in the description below and so
you're promoting to reach and find those
people and then your next step is to
close the sale okay and this part again
you might be like well I don't like
sales I don't want to be salesy it's not
about being salesy because if you could
find the right people who are looking
for a solution to the exact problems
that you can solve you don't have to be
salesy they actually want to work with
you they want to become your client and
so the biggest thing that actually stops
people from doing this I'll tell you if
you're just getting started if you've
been around the block a while you know
this already and I'm preaching to the
choir here but for those of you that
like you've never heard of this before
maybe this is your first time
hearing about starting a business like
this it's about how you think that
determines if you can produce those
results because if you're thinking is I
can't do this people aren't going to
want to hear from me I'm not sure if I'm
good enough chances are you're going to
struggle and so we got to work on that
part in our own thinking we got to let
go of perfectionism we got to let go of
the need to be perfect the world worry
and fear about what everybody is going
to think about us and and can I tell you
this is that that is actually the number
one area that stops people from being
successful in one of these businesses
it's not that the business itself is
actually hard we get caught up in our
head thinking that we can't do it that
we're not good enough that people won't
want the things that we
offer and that stops us from actually
taking action from actually putting
ourselves out there from actually taking
a risk and I've seen it happen I can
give the blueprint to every single step
to people I I have that free training
it's a total blueprint on what to do the
platforms how to do it how to put it
together in my coaching program I walk
people through step by step but until
somebody actually takes action and does
it which again there's risk involved
you're risking your reputation you're
risking what if they don't like it what
if people uh want something differently
okay you're not going to please
everybody you're not going to make
everybody happy no matter how perfect
you do everything and what that does is
when you can really start to understand
that it releases us from the pressure to
try to get it perfect and we can
literally just show up and do our best
and that's what I encourage people to do
is to do your best do your best and
forget the rest that's what Tony Horton
said and I and I love that statement
because what it means is
that you don't have to have all of the
pieces figured out
before you get started now the beautiful
part about how these businesses work is
how the math works on this you know did
you know that if you have a course that
you're selling
online and let's say that you're
charging $97 for that
course if you get a hundred people to
buy that course that is
$9700 now that might be really hard to
get a100 a to buy a course for
$97 which is why what I tell people to
do is if you charge and you add a zero
to this
$997 you only need to get 10 people and
really you only need to
get eight people to buy a course from
you every single month for
$997 to be able to make $100,000 a year
just shy of $100,000 a
year and that that's not difficult to do
now you might say why would somebody
invest ,000 into something with me
because the amount of effort that it
takes them to figure that thing out on
their own that you already know that
comes very easy to you and I'll tell you
this you want to teach in your course
the stuff that comes easy to you that's
what will make you the most amount of
money and it might even seem a little
boring like you're like that's so simple
why would somebody pay for
that the stuff that I teach I'll tell
you this it comes very simple to me
because I've been doing it a long time
and that is what builds a successful
business is if as again and again and
again I find people that need exactly
what I know that I can then pass on to
them and then they can learn to do it
themselves and I'm able to make money
every single month by doing this and so
when we can learn how to communicate
well when we can learn how to reach
those people we can learn how to find
those people then you can start to
record a course you can create an ebook
you can create a product a digital
product that you can put out there and
find those people that are actually
looking to have that problem solved for
them I want you to imagine waking up and
seeing $2,000 in your bank account that
just came in while you were sleeping
that because somebody bought a course
that you did work on two months ago that
you put out there and it solves the
problem that they're looking for
and they come to you saying whoa this is
exactly what I need exactly what I want
and you didn't have to do any additional
extra work for that other than start
finding those people and talking about
it and telling them about it that's
exactly what's possible with a business
in the online course or coaching space
is it gives you an opportunity to be
able to change your financial future it
gives you a chance to shift out of the 9
to5 shift out of having to work two jobs
shift out of being in debt to be able to
create something that is sustainable and
lifechanging for your family and so
again like I told you I have this
training right here it's completely free
you can find it in the description below
um all about how to start your own sixf
fig online course or coaching business
and then I have a coaching program where
I Mentor people every single week called
the client growth accelerator program
where I work with you through step by
step I have trainings I have
accountability I have courses I have
everything in here for you that walks
you through the process that I've helped
thousands of people over the years be
able to build six and even seven figure
businesses for themselves and so again
I'd love to help you with that as well
I'd love to walk with you through that
process get on the waiting list to jump
in with us when we open the doors to
this and I'd love to have you become a
part of our community we have a a
community of coaches and mentors where
we work with them every single week to
be able to help them get results so they
build their course and then how do they
Market it how do they find the people
that are wanting to buy that course
that's what I work with people through
is I walk you through finding your Niche
your messaging how do you close more
sales how do you promote it the right
way so that you have consistent income
so that you have massive impact so that
your life is actually doing something
powerful with what you're I'm not saying
that you're not doing anything powerful
but what I'm saying is is that you get
to do something rather than working a
job for somebody else where what you
create is having that impact and that is
what's possible with a course or online
coaching business and so I think the
best thing to do is go check out that
free class that I have that I put
together I think it'll help you I think
it's a great first step for you to get
started with that it is not as
complicated as you think it is way
simpler
then we make it that we have it thought
up in our head and I think a lot of the
things that we think about of oh I can't
do it or the reasons why we come up with
why we can't are solved when you get the
blueprint you understand exactly how to
do that so listen stay following my page
stay plugged in and go check out those
trainings that we have and I'd love to
see you start to make $100,000 this year
or more in your own business I'd love to
help you with that process to do that
we'll talk soon everybody have a good
one